Guide to the John Watts Papers, 1945-1982 MSS.093
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IX: Audio Recordings
  - Subseries C: Concerts - Live Recordings
    - May Festival Note: Master Dub/Concord String Quartet: Kosteck, Earle Brown, Crumb; 3rd annual, May 1972 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" (Box 61, Folder data_value_missing_619e5b33b5d3e1e9b10a486d5ef311fb)
    - May Festival Note: Master Reel: Fennelly (Sunyata), Salzman, Elegy, Zupko, Spiegelman, Demonstration pieces Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 61, Folder data_value_missing_f28aeb5c99fdea3e2227f0a9a59616e6)
    - May Festival Note: Performance group 1972: Cope, Baker, Koplow, Barnes, Cox, Nowak, Crego Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", 1972 00 00 (Box 61, Folder data_value_missing_ccc3353b3ad4332eb617da348d17b4d8)
    - May Festival Note: Master: Zelenka, Dahl, Turok, Carter, Adler, Dempsey Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 61, Folder data_value_missing_0b351d7d51506cdae966861b07692e57)
    - Composers Cooperative Society Note: Reel #2 Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 62, Folder data_value_missing_3ca0bc4abd07ed8cecd2495139076f30)
    - May Festival Concert Note: Guitar - 1973 Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 62, Folder data_value_missing_6945402c1cea9d4f336c21cee76b3760)
    - May Festival Note: Thorne, Clark, Johnson - 1973 Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 62, Folder data_value_missing_810c19b4aaa9826e276eb45051cd41ec)
    - May Festival Note: Tollefson Recital 1974 Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 62, Folder data_value_missing_229cc9db83535721371bead2ee6a83ef)
    - May Festival Note: The Performance Group plus Zupko, 1974 Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 62, Folder data_value_missing_6ff67aded1c4bc27869de165f29950fa)
    - May Festival Note: Composers Festival Orchestra 1974 Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 62, Folder data_value_missing_f3b5680352cb9168cb0e02706b0884a0)
    - May Festival Note: Composers String Ensemble 1974 Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 62, Folder data_value_missing_0f9f577e681bacf844e3708030340ead)
  - Subseries D: Commercial Works
    - Ad Agency Sampler Note: Master Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 62, Folder data_value_missing_39c8d60ff588d3a850b514b17509b2e4)
    - Ad Agency Sampler Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 62, Folder data_value_missing_8d6098b9900d0d60d6cf85011e4dcfc3)
    - Ad Agency Sampler Note: Copy of Revised Ad Sampler Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 62, Folder data_value_missing_b0e1577112fffaa9db3d192df2209050)
    - Ad Agency Sampler Note: Master of New Ad Sampler Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 62, Folder data_value_missing_4a04799f8dfc130f44d437cfd0910a0e)
    - Reeves Sound Note: Judi Pissaro's Voice in Mixes, 4-track Brand: Agfa Format: 1/2", undated (Box 62, Folder data_value_missing_97be7e4d2c1345f5ae8e356483f0e231)
    - Reeves Sound Note: Voice Mixes [sampler] Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 62, Folder data_value_missing_0b8832979d5970c8dcd7265789749f82)
    - Good News Excerpts" Note: 7.5 ips Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_a687f602116b49a0df2ada35aaa892bd)
    - Gordon Glyn Commercials Note: Master Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_7c99a8d3e4ac07dbc46a9cc55eada84c)
    - May Festival Radio Spot Note: Vth festival Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_3aee51beff4bd7c65ea6068fd65a6e05)
    - National Public Radio Spots Note: 15ips Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_0d7d0320e8d69f753263dadf8ce99f1a)
    - Commercial Works - Continued, undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_b66ad01fba9f8361965b18ce48a9aa84)
    - Radio Program- Watts Note: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_87f0c33e072d02e37a68869eba249844)
    - Odetta Spots for Aware Week Note: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_d18ce9b1be23b4ffdc9c83db31fe2310)
    - Odetta Spots for Aware Week Note: 7.5 ips Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4"sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_a3fcb9091dabe682df3c9d1888635c30)
    - TV Logos Note: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_a2cadba17406e1a1c9116d303134c464)
    - Radio Ad- CT, Ben Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_cd85a8823cf142c6f233d054bb16d51a)
    - Commercials, ABC Jet Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_72eecac7204c68f83acb5e78c55d0659)
    - Radio Ad - Smirnoff Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_621b564ee975e532736028ee27cfac16)
    - Radio program-Gladys Foreman Note: Radio KGBS Los Angeles Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_c7c66834591ec1c2682b093c26a3e056)
    - Commercials Note: Two Segments Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_dfbf9cf3e4b7e722ff409c3f6a54712e)
    - Radio Ad, CT Note: Frank Spaghetti Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_f7ad60f5e2d511d2a33bfad6ab134e32)
    - Radio Ad CT, Xmas Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_d2c6c258221221077165a27d89fe4cfc)
    - Radio Ad CT, Ben Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_51d735b8d0a9b5814f4f119e4c2f5cef)
    - WBAI John's broadcast Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_e048959b55acb25b296c1b62197bb1cf)
    - NPR Spots FTM Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_f682c0ee3d425e24367235ec161456c5)
    - Ad Sampler Note: Use as master Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_f89ff27b58b99d55465c3b8eb42e3ae1)
    - NPR Spots FTM Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_25663b9b479838ed8d87c991445d03fb)
    - NPR Spots FTM Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_4a0eb8f59275e88a7549391e9b7f38a9)
    - Ad Sampler No. 2 Note: Master, incl. Gordon-Glyn commercial Laura's Interview 1/4 sm. Brand: interview with Marion Honosko WBAI Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_d638ca2c29b1b9826ce24bdb176d6ac6)
    - Poverty Note: Fragment of Hubie's dialogue Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_a6498b2f54ebed02048a276c9af8cb5b)
    - Interview Note: Tape made at Franks Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_7bfc1bf1d6f303bdfd5e4f67091e506d)
    - Peace Rally Central Park Note: 1969 Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_236bd00b4ef4877a6fc0e8181fb78cda)
    - St. Peter's tape - Watts Note: stereo Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_8b8ab38fef76d7a4032c5446835c8050)
    - Drug Interviews Note: sample dub Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_98101202f763eb5b5a2e3528b84b1ce1)
    - Haygood Note: 1966 Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_5248e06dad28f5e1f4a7a4e391b8b786)
    - Electronic Score Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_6827aac053fcdb61f36b848c2833e7fc)
    - Discussion - New School Note: Hodes moderator, Bull/Hodes/Foreman/Wolfe; de Oca/ Wendy Stein, G. Torino, Nov. 1972. Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_939fcef5c60046f8aac1d57b3200aad7)
    - New School Q & A Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_89bd773a35adac66d8f2f0b2b8a8e464)
    - WBAI on McDonagh's lecture Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_5fcf662658302c4709a7de1ccb205c5c)
    - McDonagh's lecture, with intro by Laura Foreman Format: 1/4"sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_622b49a9315ddf405979ad626c72e8f4)
    - Quotations and "Om" Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_29541ca9817a918b633343a1444fcc00)
    - Family Watts in Tennessee Note: 3" reel, sent in mail from Tennessee to Mr. & Mrs. Watts in New York Format: 1/4", undated (Box 63, Folder data_value_missing_4115b08407be04e15bc9bebb8b328327)
  - Subseries E: Sound Effects and Element Tapes
    - Sound Effects Note: Tape fall Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 64, Folder data_value_missing_2aaa85dd262cfd4a700648bd77489687)
    - Sound Effects Note: Brook V Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 64, Folder data_value_missing_379c6eb7e18a1830f51cb72a456b0f0e)
    - Sound Effects Note: Debussy Faun Electronic Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 64, Folder data_value_missing_4ca043e94244f3bd0bc5642b4a822b0b)
    - Sound Effects Note: Brook I Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 64, Folder data_value_missing_d6623513c10b4de72d56ce98a2978948)
    - Sound Effects Note: Bullfight Sounds Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 64, Folder data_value_missing_565b107f124cc29855669a52b076b392)
    - Sound Effects Note: Marches, Militaire Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 64, Folder data_value_missing_a08ab771079337198cb74ceb62426c7f)
    - Sound Effects Note: Brook II Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 64, Folder data_value_missing_808651a057b5c9a61f1c978227b22868)
    - Sound Effects Note: Surf Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 64, Folder data_value_missing_9ce1c9f22b5ff3c506a71e4efbedd262)
    - Sound Effects Note: Bells, Rain, for RR Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 64, Folder data_value_missing_6103800803192c82e53d7ce1781ce217)
    - Sound Effects Note: Scratch- Do not use Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 64, Folder data_value_missing_b312ce2fe9a1c290004160b2506b488b)
    - Radio Sounds Note: Radio bits, changing stations, Kennedy... Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 64, Folder data_value_missing_b8a0b7b3c14ebc8a571b4a9af302c0ef)
    - Sound Effects Note: TV Baseball game Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 64, Folder data_value_missing_573ee43a18d669023b8f84533e0be9cf)
    - Sound Effects Note: ARP drone Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 64, Folder data_value_missing_d38f5fb0c90254ed964be8704718d399)
    - Sound Effects Note: Locrian Working tape with footsteps Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 64, Folder data_value_missing_49d416afedeeb3871d8de24292f4e37a)
    - Sound Effects Note: Riot Sounds Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 64, Folder data_value_missing_e508ed8c0131e67ad76da3fa7736f447)
    - Sound Effects Note: Random synthesizer sounds-for Signals Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 64, Folder data_value_missing_94db6f958044d039fd1c0414fad0c18f)
    - Sound Effects Note: Chicken Little, do not use Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 64, Folder data_value_missing_41f9583503e4bac9ac27f267be8afae6)
    - Sound Effects Note: Collection of Sobs Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 64, Folder data_value_missing_e1d6e005fb54be2691e892cc383fd39f)
    - Sound Effects Note: Improvisation, TV, Clock ticking Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 64, Folder data_value_missing_a566f8e6010fc850828a0fd9588d54f0)
    - Sound Effects Note: Boos from Watts Electric, 1977 Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_e194f396f5848b59677181012599aeff)
    - Sound Effects Note: Rain Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_f1a9d35989b0760ccd031f4ebff7c6f4)
    - Sound Effects Note: Foggy Mountain Dew Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_2f4a61617d37372540e447433476248d)
    - Sound Effects Note: Brook III Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_f33bdc015516a972825fc798bb97b33e)
    - Sound Catalog Note: to accompany An Electronic Studio Manual by Ronald Pellegrino, Ohio State Univ. 1968-69 Format: 1/4" sm., 1968-1969 (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_55ee7dd5982dbf1c4825fad49665adc7)
    - Sound Effects Note: Cass. Background stereo Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_493bad48574a29fffb135285cc14bcf2)
    - Sound Effects Note: Answerphone message tape Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_27175067e8395f28734bc7e8db30aa93)
    - Sound Effects Note: Telephone Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_00421119729859293d080a83ef1f41a0)
    - Sound Effects Note: This is not a working number Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_4a7d4b59623cea1cdf78ab212ae753ee)
    - Sound Effects Note: Brook IV Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_2e3825db798f7522390cd93e72fcad3f)
    - Sound Effects Note: Rain Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_bf8285cc7e83fd9d9777e3c52e7c3578)
    - Sound Effects Note: Brook I-A Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_121684259cbb3826b78c2052095f33e3)
    - Sound Effects Note: Sound of tape unwinding Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_30d5d379fe84ff6f9a3a8f49e664b66a)
    - Sound Effects Note: Brook III Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_c0f5658c2fb5509e4df911119a86cecc)
    - Sound Effects Note: Bells Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_adad4c843f69644cb159758c314b7c8a)
    - Sound Effects Note: Old Time Pickin' Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_bf5c44cf6e3e9351dd6db1ff278d260f)
    - Sound Effects Note: Mother Nature Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_73dbe66f591a611b3ea0b223223700f1)
    - Sound Effects Note: Mother Nature Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_36179206b41109b6e0d787ec2098ca9d)
    - Sound Effects Note: Mother Nature Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_cc63ce2beda73f4e4796c5b272b016f1)
    - Radio and TV bits Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_ea2fb8ba8b15c47e07a0b7dd8a3d918f)
    - Sound Effects Note: Feliciano, Star Spangeled Banner Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_2a19919c5ec73759d39ab8327ba86907)
    - Sound Effects Note: Oral Roberts Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_632cc81c065c018efd199758a30a5757)
    - Sound Effects Note: Telephone Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_0f8b2187353b653e08dcf7d9e823062d)
    - Sound Effects Note: Go Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_570f70edb408ebb9c5c6732fc6f155c8)
    - Sound Effects Note: Audience Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_23e0354be95f7179c94d5f728bf18f9a)
    - New School ARP Class Note: Spring 1972 Working Tape Format: 1/2" (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_5660164c796edc27fc4117e4dcc6277c)
    - Schatz, Warren Note: Ballerina Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_a4b52d098fcc154e630ac44b7a4dbc38)
    - Mecox takes Note: crude mix Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_0297e33859df5a9a87c75318c383ad05)
    - Watts Note: Final Master Discards Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_9f8b7330eee1f4f49e4020950cfa7036)
    - Unidentified Note: What? Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_50f309b058d18a44ff78a250fca49259)
    - Unidentified Note: Leftover from Reel #4, Illinois Piano Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_3a897c1b2fdc591ac0109876786d2c93)
    - Unidentified Note: Sound track mix down Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_3b873a7087c1aa22c0ad4ac456202692)
    - Unidentified Note: Sound track tails Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_831e078cd7e64e413db85bbb8cde816f)
  - Subseries F: Audio Cassettes
    - Mas Note: Realized on the ARP 2500 and 2600 Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_94619caf8c714f5e8ac4b69e37fb0111)
    - Keepsakes Note: Sage City Symphony Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_8613f5572742fffe239591447f63aa71)
    - Keepsakes Note: Sage City Symphony Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_445fcb51752aa49b7e21cbbc771f6dcc)
    - Time Coded Woman Note: Cooper Union Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_8a750f7fe03d3d094a59b20e0aef4be6)
    - Keepsakes Note: Sage City Symphony Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_f156e8119c9efeb5da534972b6241f03)
    - Laugharne Note: Background tape Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_9c1049aae60d322dc3f9847f8b69eaa2)
    - Laugharne Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_44d2e38becb7a5460831e63259e45fdb)
    - Keepsakes Note: Background tape Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_f980384776fad01b86c93489f9b708a8)
    - Keepsakes Note: Background tape Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_7dc30e30b044bef2cb9a745db981ebe4)
    - Mas, Ups, Processional Elegy, Piano for Te Tutti Note: Background tape Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_0d1ceb6e0676c1dd41616ef1a0fdf529)
    - Griffith Rose Note: 2nd Alto Concerto Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_bed38c670ba042c15ccd92334d722507)
    - Songanddance Program" Note: Rough dub Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_c20990e9d087f62f7a3def45d3349034)
    - Police Calls Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_26ecf84f02bced4dc0c96b8f3d899105)
    - Reunion I & II Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_495d9257a97e2a082d792e754d308a73)
    - Home Tape Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_4a1e6252c96548ffaaa4d27d7836b952)
    - Athens Note: 2 tapes Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_3257e143bfd41308e55f1726b4dfb69b)
    - Hillbilly Note: 2 tapes Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_1115952fba63e3f776c79c62ee10c74f)
    - Ear Food Note: Music of Brian Flahive & Dana McCurdy Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_a69be024103a32f9e1969e0fd2d95a74)
    - Music Museum Atlanta Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_766b9443fe54cd5049ad4fa9d7ed5410)
    - Tomorrow's Television Tonight Note: Nick Yanni with Laura, John, and others, Channel D- Manhattan, 1979 Format: Audio cass. (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_113e6886d38dd65a6d136334be22a958)
    - Religious America Note: Channel 13, 1974 California Revival Meeting Format: Audio cass. (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_f0d148b0053cabfdaf09f3f4a888ff77)
    - Stein piece audio samples Note: Gershwin, Satie, Berg, Joplin, etc. Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_4c00e52a302858106b092b7440ce3fee)
    - Time Coded Woman ? Note: found in john's cassette next to his bed [after he died]" Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_03d51b5f197efff048c9da5a9af53087)
    - Watts Interview with W. Duckworth Note: Tapes 1 and 2 of 2; Dec. 29, 1981 Format: Audio cass. (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_8d6369d95f089c06d78b91c29d5215c4)
    - Match de Boxe Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_d564d76ab49ec90a610d2d4164e84c86)
    - Laugharne Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_0ece6067a38e3f386212869eb9acf8e0)
    - Various pieces Note: MAS, ACH, Barbro Variatons on Radio Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_3d80aa2d2262538a2a445d23e3e4ae51)
    - Ulf Grahn's The Visit Note: The Visit Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_43771e362fdcde54d951f0b628b6b31f)
    - John's answering machine tape Note: Messages from friends in the days after he died- people calling Laura to find out what happened and to offer sympathy. Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_086aaae613f27ceee6491479ccbfb805)
    - Vermont Auction Note: home made tape Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_00ca7ea557c50e472e4372bfee39a57d)
    - Vermont Fiddlers Note: home made tape Format: Audio cass., undated (Box 66, Folder data_value_missing_3d2b59cb7286e03e4eab51e4b74dd055)
  - Subseries G: Vinyl Records
    - Laura Foreman Song Note: More'n a Year (1966) pop song sung by Charlie Brown Format: 45rpm (Box 67, Folder data_value_missing_468917ff1a85d2bc7f2f3a6b1ea3f05c)
    - Trilogy Records Note: Test Pressings; Format: 33 1/3 and 78 rpm, undated (Box 67, Folder data_value_missing_9f37bf54da196843511f32286a9e1966)
    - Knoxville Symphony 1950 Note: (Something by Watts, doesn't say what piece) Format: 33 1/3 (Box 67, Folder data_value_missing_36e6e7b145231aaccfb28874215f2db0)
    - Music of John Watts, Vol. 1: Elegy to Chimney: In Memoriam, for trumpet and tape; Piano For Te, for piano and 13+ players; Mots D'heures: Gousses, Rames, for Voices and tape Note: Serenus 12080 Format: 33 1/3, undated (Box 67, Folder data_value_missing_d15f4e623ac79266bdffbe87adf685b7)
    - Contemporary Piano Project played by Dwight Peltzer: Raoul Pleskow: Pentimento; John Watts: Sonata for Piano; Alvin Brehm: Variations; Charles Bestor: Piano Sonata; Note: Serenus 12069 Format: 33 1/3, undated (Box 67, Folder data_value_missing_12e3d8a55a7862c5bf8aa56574bc3f5f)
    - Composers Festival Orchestra conducted by Alvin Brehm: David Foley: Four Pieces for a Saturday Afternoon; Robert Keys Clark: Concerto for Clarinet and Chamber Orchestra; John Watts: Signals for Soprano and Chamber Orchestra; Alvin Brehm: Cycle of 6 Songs on poems of Garcia-Lorca. Note: Trilogy CTS 1002 Format: 33 1/3, undated (Box 67, Folder data_value_missing_eb6a08684c3cca6085ea717099fe4ea3)
    - Dean Sanders, Pianist, plays William Albright, Burrill Phillips, Johns Watts:William Albright: Pianoagogo; Burrill Phillips: First Piano Sonata; Second Piano Sonata; John Watts: Sonata for Piano Note: Trilogy CTS 1003 Format: 33 1/3, undated (Box 67, Folder data_value_missing_eab657eccfe46675515170b65a8ca641)
    - Iowa Brass Quintet: Two Studies: Allan Blank; Three Diverse Movements: Newel Kay Brown; Opus 58: John Huggler; Suite: Verne Reynolds Note: Trilogy CTS 1001 Format: 33 1/3, undated (Box 67, Folder data_value_missing_5d1817b3984aeac72d648ba468413919)
    - Vinyl Audio Recordings: Various recordings - John Watts personal music collection; Laura's dance class selections (background etc.) Format: 33 1/3 rpm, a few 45rpm, undated (Box 68)
    - Vinyl Audio Recordings: Various recordings - John Watts personal music collection; Laura's dance class selections (background etc.) Format: 33 1/3 rpm, a few 45rpm, undated (Box 69)
    - Vinyl Audio Recordings: Various recordings - John Watts personal music collection; Laura's dance class selections (background etc.) Format: 33 1/3 rpm, a few 45rpm, undated (Box 70)
    - Vinyl Audio Recordings: Various recordings - John Watts personal music collection; Laura's dance class selections (background etc.) Format: 33 1/3 rpm, a few 45rpm, undated (Box 71)
    - Vinyl Audio Recordings: Various recordings - John Watts personal music collection; Laura's dance class selections (background etc.) Format: 33 1/3 rpm, a few 45rpm, undated (Box 72)
    - Vinyl Audio Recordings: Various recordings - John Watts personal music collection; Laura's dance class selections (background etc.) Format: 33 1/3 rpm, a few 45rpm, undated (Box 73)
  - Subseries H: Audio Recordings - Access Copies
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
    - Glass and Shadows, [undated]; ID: 093.0119 (Box Shared Fales 125, Cd 093.0119)
      General note
      Format: CD-R
      TRT: 00:02:57
      Original Format: 1/2" reel to reel
    - Heirlooms - Sections 1 and 2, [undated]; ID: 093.0122 (Box Shared Fales 125, Cd 093.0122)
      TRT: 00:15:34
      Original Format: 1/4" reel to reel